What led you to coming to Indianapolis?
Um, if you had other interests, what put
them over the top for you?
>> I mean, I felt like this was a a good
situation for me with the with D with
the guys in the Dline realm, the head
coach and his mentality, how you know
tax was a good perfect fit for me.
>> Joel, go ahead.
>> What do you uh what do you think has has
been such a good fit for you in Kansas
City over the years?
I mean, with their scheme, it kind of
works with uh how the whole the whole
defense kind of works together. Uh it
kind of just all meshes together in a
way like no handled everything, how he
wants certain position to attack the the
scheme. Um allowing, you know, the run
efforts handled what they need to do and
def
rushers attack the way they need to do
need to attack. Uh it was very balanced
for what we did there. Did did you
mostly play nos over there?
>> Yes. Uh occasionally they'll have me at
three. Uh depending on what type of
scheme we're running that week. Uh it
just varies.
>> Chap.
>> It's easy for players to be pigeon
holed. Are you more than a run stuffer?
That's kind of what you hang your head
on.
>> I definitely hang my hat on stopping a
run, but I definitely have um I can
definitely rush the passer. like a lot
of times if we have the right we have
definitely a lot of fantastic uh pass
rushers in our at our disposal. So we
definitely want to use them more times
than not.
>> Again, look at the resume with with the
Super Bowls. I think you started three I
think three of the four with KC. What
what what experience does that bring
with you that that you can that kind of
helps you move forward and maybe share
with your teammates?
I mean, it got goes with um a lot of
things that that are involved with it,
whether it's stuff that's on the field
or stuff that goes on off the field. A
lot of things that involve, you know, a
lot of sacrifices, a lot of uh
discipline, diligence, and a lot of
things we got to do on the little
things, a lot of small details here and
there that can make or break a win, a
playoff run, or a Super Bowl win or
loss.
Do I read it right? That you had an
injury the one Super Bowl. You're right.
The triceps or elbow, whatever it was.
Is that right?
>> Yes, that's correct. Okay,
>> cool. Thank you,
>> Joel. Go ahead.
>> I know you spent most of your playing
time in Kansas City, but what did you
learn from uh from being in training
camp with the Jets last year?
Um, one of the biggest things I've
learned a lot of thing I was trying to
pick Qu's brain because of how he
operates with things. Um, a lot of times
where how I go about my game and how he
goes about his game is just really a lot
of times it's just attacking. Come out
your come out your stance really just
getting off a lot of key reads. Um cuz
when I was with the Jets, it was a
different type of scheme, a different
type of uh mentality where when I was
with Kansas City, it was more read
attack. For the Jets, it was the quite
opposite where they just more attacked
than read. And it took me a time to
really get used to that. And it just
that's why I was really just picking his
brain on how to really just how to
balance with that and get get more
comfortable with that. um just finding
the the right gears to kind of get used
to it. Um because like like I said, it's
a different type of scheme, different
type of defense, and just it's sometimes
a little difficult to to quickly adapt
to it. But with the guys I had in in my
in the DI room, I felt like I was I was
doing well.
>> Just a few more, James.
>> All right. Not a very serious question,
but bear with me. Um, how do you feel
about dropping in coverage? Lou likes to
mix it up and you got to pick on Philip
Rivers back in the day.
>> Hey, I'm off for you.
I mean, wait, whatever it takes, I'm off
for anything that need to do, I got it.
>> Gotcha. And then on a more serious note,
when you have survived where you have
the NFL, um, you know, coming in as a
third round pick and then, you know,
signing the one-year deals or getting
traded and coming back, like what has
kept you going when you don't always
know where you're going to be yeartoear?
I mean, I always kind of tell myself no
matter what goes on, wherever goes my
way, whatever it doesn't go my way, to
try to do my best to stay consistent.
Um, the saying I always tell myself,
chop wood, carry water. You know, no
matter what goes on, just keep doing
what you're doing. Um, not a phrase. I
always tell myself, be where your feet
are and just keep focused on what's
important now. you know, regardless if
things are going right or wrong, as long
as I stay consist of what I got to do,
things are always going to turn around
the way they needs to be.
>> And then what's your relationship like
with Chavarious Ward? I know you all
over overlapped a little bit in Kansas
City.
>> Yeah. Oh my goodness. You know what?
Everybody in the field has been asking
you some guys that I've I've known and
it just hit me. I just forgot about my
dog Mooney. Like that's really that's my
dude. Like uh man, I can't wait to see
him actually. He's a good guy. Um, I
hope he's doing well. I know that
there's a lot been a lot of things that
are going on with him that I have
to reach out to. I'm sorry about that.
But definitely, um, I look forward to
seeing him.